I hope all of the ready to come out of the city council.
Do they generate a fee?
Do they do?
Do you come up with the question?
What's the question?
Pressure?
You know, one thing's the way to wrap it.
What do you mean you can't wait round?
We're going to have it for three months.
Put the family.
We had property about the city.
I said something.
We had some neighbors of ours.
On the Rock Hill Red.
It was a very long time ago.
We had 20 10 mark.
G.E.S. looking on the street.
We had 2,500.
21.
The three Rock Hill is the car.
21.5.
21.11.
It was brought to my attention by our neighbors that we have a lot of trouble.
We're going to get their mail on the car side of the red.
We're going to get a county.
And so I'll talk to each of the neighbors.
These businesses.
They all express concern.
And a fear for the lives of our neighbors.
We're going to make the first steps.
So it happens that their mailboxes are in the soil along our property.
We're not in the city today.
I think actually the district set is the work that we're living in.
We're going to work more as we are our property.
It's what we're going to do.
First of all, I'd like to take on the passenger service.
We've access a lot of time.
And that's what we're going to do.
We would like to do this at some time, and ordinance or something, put on the agenda, but you know, as you've used that, or as you've made it, it's something that each or hopefully sooner than later, basically say,
local ordinance says, hey, we have to have your mailbox and your property in the city of Miami and the poor, the permission of the layman or the one installer and a lot's on.
The reason why we want that ordinance is that we like to take that to the postmaster and say, hey, here's a little ordinance, the postmaster has to apply by that ordinance and local rules laws, and then they could.
So that's not the best brush, or whatever, but.
And then I talk about the mailboxes, you know, with a tent that brush all of you, we'd like to make it to the property, make it look nice and city, you know, interaction,
and that's really the reason to request this one of the public requests, one or more of the council put that on the agenda.
And as far as the reduction, we're very thrilled about that.
I think the city could acquire, you know, crushing you.
There's nothing like tears, asphalt, concrete house.
We would definitely have a 400 cubic yards of use concrete from the old,
thought horse property, it doesn't have a recar end of you.
We'd definitely have to have a roof base for the city to be used in the build.
And we'd definitely be in the middle of the building between the heat and turn.
And 609 a day, we weren't anywhere up in the city to help you guys out.
You can provide a brand-made security role in the build of a base in the cost of using construction projects.
So if you guys had a pressure, we'd bring the kind of thing you can use it,
as you saw that, you know, a good charge.
So I'm going to appreciate your knowledge.
Great, because if you didn't get that right,
then you could provide four to five.
Five.
Six, first base.
My older generation was just in your 20.
20.
But then I got it.
This was on.
Send.
We have here for me.
Maybe you can go, but it's good to see you and first off I wanted to thank you for having us back.
I'm a partner with Oregon, so since we're a CPA firm with offices in Edmund and Oklahoma City.
And I have very large board of art practice is government laws.
We have this whole entities like the City of Miami, similar in size, and City's larger and smaller than you are.
In addition to that, we have audit of members gain agencies, private governments, pieces of travel governments, all those things,
said they're in the large part of our practice.
I come to you tonight without very much to say.
And I find that an interesting position, because I know it's some respect to feel like we had done better job.
And we brought you findings at the same time.
And we're going to tell you, I do deliver findings to things.
Those are not clients that our firm tends to retain.
And the reason is, because we're a fairly disrespectful person.
We like to work on clients who do a good job.
Do the things that they need to do to keep the staff that they need to ask.
And the City of Miami is doing a great job.
that you have adequate staff in the place to do a good job. And then you have outsource contractors
in place who come in before we do. And so your corporate associates firm comes in and
up for a city staff. They come in and work on the application. From our point of view, they
work for the management. And they come in and help make sure everything's done right.
And you're getting clean financial statements to audit. I can tell you that firm takes it as
a personal approach when we do that one. So it sends them to go, you know, try to figure out
how to make this something. So this is where you're at. You're at a very good position.
You're audit opinions or what the current term for is unbounded. You used to call that clean
opinion. You will find that opinion as a couple of pages long. But what I can tell you
about that means unbounded by it. It means it's all standardized language in there. Everything
that's written there is a standard language for work. And a lot of opinion we haven't got in and
sorted explaining anything while putting any except for or disclaimers or adverse type words in there.
So that is good news for the city of Miami. And so thank you. I encourage you to appreciate
the work that you're staff and the relationship with your outsourced consultants. And really
the money that the city dedicates to that function is doing the job that you're spending
the money to do. So with that, like I said, I could come with you. Kind of in the hand
I do you mention you have your financial statement on it and front of you, that's the big amount
of document that you can find on the front. We did also issue a single lot of report. You don't always
have a single article. What triggers that is if the city spins more than $750,000 of federal
government training. You are over that awarding year and year on it. So we did have
to issue a single lot. When we do a single lot of what happens is we select major programs.
Then those major programs get audited or compliance with grant agreement, reporting all the things
of the grant box. On your single lot of this year, a good one major program. And that
was the coronavirus relief funds. And I mean, it's pretty clear if you just look at your
grant money is why that would be a B major program. I mean major program is driven by just like,
what it sounds like, what was what were the jumbo.
And that was it.
It also did not result in any findings.
And then it was extended appropriately.
But I do want to make myself available for any questions.
And I'm going to read my address and anything
on to my request.
That's the answer.
Can't answer all that back to you with the response to our argument.
But eventually, and I can speak to you,
and to make it function like a financial decision.
I will tell you in your staff
and probably do a better job of that than I can.
Programme associates there for sale.
That's part of what you pay them for.
This is how you hold that as well.
The reason you want to help them change how this artworks,
that document is practiced by your manager.
Programme associates does it on your behalf.
I can say that function is an extension of your manager team.
Our job is to modify it.
But we don't work.
We don't track them down.
So that's why I say that.
Your manager, I think we can hear outside consultative.
Let's speak to that.
And work efficiently.
I don't know.
So you've got no issues, you're making me good.
Yeah.
We did have some adjusting entries.
There were some adjustments to the books.
I think three adjusting entries would be exact towards
something medical liability.
They're their rules around those.
Those were both sit down, and they were playing down
the poor report was issued.
So that was there were no adjusted entries.
So there was no stand-off in the city management.
I think you need to change this.
And you need to do that forward this time.
So it shouldn't actually say, it wasn't the zero issues,
but that's significant issues.
So the only thing I'd like to add is that it is,
it is unique that that's such another wonderful one.
And you're back in the year, which is my visit, it's very interesting.
The only downside that is something that is important in critical
for our manager, we're well-being, becomes kind of the one making it.
And I think it is a good problem.
It's a good problem that we're not in the year discussing
and I'm very glad we can have a good response
and a lot of you can meditate in the rest.
Good thing is.
And that makes sense and enriched sure that we have lots of lives, lots of outside lives.
And looking at our books, we'll be in our processes, we'll be able to find how we're operating and what we're doing.
Because we don't know what to say, and we've got the proper associates, which does our handling and consulting.
They can only come in and make sure that, well, we're doing a turn-a-little's accurate and appropriate,
all these works that we come in and take it.
And then another thing comes in on it, we overall process and appropriate testing and looking for issues.
And from that perspective, this is a great thing to me this work.
You all know, the position that we've had.
And I guess, I actually, in good position, we're not struggling, we're not trying to make other things.
That, and we haven't totally enough of that.
We track our revenues and expenses extensively, and we haven't taken much of process.
We all work together to transfer your clothes to come up with the best, but just hospitals and buy services for everybody that we have.
That being said, you know, that can accommodate that.
If we didn't have a lot of the money, just if we had bad items, it wouldn't be treated as close as possible,
but if you've got to know your number, you've got to charge your money.
So that being said, it certainly makes my job easy coming in here.
I've got here in here, here I go.
We have a clean financial, and here you're later, we still have a lot of money.
So the great position to be, it's a good position.
It's a good position that I inherited.
It's a clean on maintaining every step of the way, and it can appreciate the whole support.
In contracts that we have in place, and the problem associates, all the associates, and all the work they've done at this position.
So if we can't say you're in a transfer, if you can look at our systems and buy and say,
if you know what money is, you can make it hopefully.
If we were to, we would be able to call them down on it.
That's something we have to know.
That's a great problem.
Thank you.
It is a good problem that I have.
I just just fear about what you're seeing after a set of that.
We do have a client, a city client right now, who's missing grant money.
They can't, you can't apply for grants, because they can't get there all about.
Because we can't make where we need to be with that, that does have.
We have another city, a little bit of a city, who has a debt ready to issue, and they're being advised to know, trying to issue.
Because you've got so many fine weeks, that the debt of buyers are going to get that, and I'm very sure, interest rates.
And you want to just sit on that and try to clean the salt before we try to issue debt.
So, bad things do happen from these.
I see it happen from there to seeing it happen in 2022, so we're in a very good position
and we want to value that and try to see it there.
Thank you for all of your effort.
Thank you for all of the staff involved.
And we'll do the finance stuff.
We're going to step up towards the order.
We'll do that position.
We'll do that.
Thank you.
So, the cost of creating life is a big reward.
I'm not going to let us talk.
I'm trying to say that.
I am the odd accounting coordinator.
We wanted to take off our separate ways.
And we would like to play in that day for April 29th.
And the 6th and 9th.
And now I have lessons that I want to do.
There are a lot of things we're down there.
We have a really good turnout.
We hope to make $5,000.
We make 16.
So, we wanted to do it again this year.
This year we are going to make some changes.
We wanted to do this.
We want to do this.
And we have to make sure.
Last year, we had some complaints that people felt that were too disconnected.
With the car show, everything, the driver made.
And then the dolls and the band.
And everything.
And we were going to try to do everything to make sure.
And we talked to each other in your office.
We would like to close off the road between.
And we had a private hospital.
And the end.
We had a private hospital.
And a cult organization.
But our food trucks on one side.
The band on the other.
And then still have our car show.
And crews on the.
So.
We had people who had the group 66 hours in the last year.
We took them down to all of us.
And they got stressed them.
They need to wait.
They even called them.
They did this for shady gatherings at the time.
So, we had classes of work.
Very businesses.
And we just wanted to curate and get them.
Get on the calendar.
You all went the last year.
We.
Unfortunately, it's exciting.
We have the trying to finish.
She's trying to get excited.
You said, what?
Talk to us.
Yeah.
We saw the injury to the same person.
We didn't get ready to write up until.
We drank.
I don't know.
There's, well, there's, in this position.
Mr. Tobks.
All right, that was great. Thank you guys.
Thanks for joining the moment.
I'm Raise Can Out Of Work.
And are they at Burger?
To Dubai Founder.
Well, better for various scientists to
fill up the central very small partnership.
I know on the wrong letter, we've been talking for
all the problem two years.
I think they came here for a couple of years ago, and we started to
conversation with some gross ideas like that, but that's just amazing program and some things
that we're in the city, they have presented to the airport board, therefore the board is very supportive of our concepts.
And this is a George Presgo.
Remember, rise on let him, I take through the planning.
Council, I appreciate the time of the night, I'm going to be free and I'm going to understand how it's going to be of our three jet works.
I'm going to give you the time to do what I'm going to do and where I have to go.
I'm going to do this county in the city for corporations.
In 2012, my young son was sitting at a German person behind the city.
He's been very ill-class.
He didn't sit there two at the same time.
We have since lost that young class and I think my son is still struggling with the
influence in the current year in 2014.
By the grace of God, he's still with him.
So through this action, I was kind of forced by the willing money into thinking about the ideation of what we do for children of our family.
In that process, I began learning with the rise of my new foundation.
I'm learning.
I've worked for the personal transparency for a small town of 66 and solving the development.
But I wrote a grant for the U.S.D.A. on the Catholic rise of education foundation.
Studying agriculture and ideation centers.
It was fun.
And through that, we began to study and work on the development of this humble town.
And through the birth of parents' parents, the R.U.J.
which pays my consulting firm $1 a year.
This is not a project.
I personally benefited from it.
I worked with the rise of education foundation.
I didn't pay the salary within that.
Then the shape you were grateful.
This is important to me this person.
And the reason for me is I think we need to do some work here.
And I really need to do it.
So we had to figure it out in the world bank.
To be free projects in our account.
One of them is to develop a handy equipment.
Training facility where we can train young veterans in their family members.
I operate in a very real handy equipment.
And then the use of that in the mediation of this process country.
And through that we did something in the other projects that we can build veterans.
And that's how we've been around the end of the work.
In this process, it's because the rise of education in the old lives house.
I see the R.F. anger in the baby.
And then there are discussions which you five side of us are talking about, what can we do with the R&P and the city board?
That's a big piece of history for our community.
We want to revitalize that and you're all trying to be this area.
And so through today, please understand, we're not going to ask the city for a month.
We have our, we want to be partners with the city and the county to create something dynamic in our community.
That benefits and brings jobs to our community, well paying the jobs.
And so through those efforts, we've made our energy networks.
I hope that you will find the value and the partnership with us.
Long-term, we want to be a good part of the community.
We want to reinvent the funding federal projects through my young woman.
So I hope, you know, I pray you'll listen there to the exciting project.
And again, thank you very much.
Mr. Storm.
Well, thank you, Jim, for your time.
I think that's an important thing in the CEO of our big networks.
I've had the privilege of meeting a right there in the organization.
And I really enjoyed what they had that they had offered to fix and with our business model.
We operate FVOs, make this in a fair operation.
And hopefully, thanks for lots of things.
That's been our plan for a long time through the whatsoever.
And we support our veterans.
And through that, they did for months a lot of hammering.
I said, look at them from here.
So I'm very, very good at it.
The aerospace has been in the aerospace business for 15 years now.
And I'm very, very, very, very, very proud of this.
I'm still in the education industry.
So what up?
Next slide, please.
One of the opportunities we see here in Markdown, too.
We would like to part of the rise.
And with them, to selfless of a life, with their selfless,
fear-long relationship.
For any of you, some aircraft here, start to do a recycling from right here.
If you want to be there, put a second on it.
And then, we'll recycling the minimum of leather.
If you want their veterans to know that.
There are about 500,000 pilots shortage from being here.
Within the next 10 years, 10 to 12 years, that's just in the United States.
Worldwide.
We're really, really, really pilot.
That's just pilots.
That doesn't include any big advantage.
the United States Department of Hospitality, Air Force Services,
Residence, Residence, and Residence Operations,
the whole industry is hurting and losing this like many other groups.
So what we can believe is to break into the table,
to a part of the services, education, and education,
air traffic control, right there at my point at a facility.
These kids will spend a year from 96 to 103,000 dollars
to get a break for air traffic control in 2% of the washouts
for the different countries.
In the United States, we've got to be a better United program
if you can't help.
and the inhibition program and we don't hope to make that inspiring as well.
Next slide, please.
So, some of the opportunities we feel we can bring to the table here, where we're paying
down, and I'm not just looking at the recycle, but some of them are excited.
We have a couple of lectures in the bowling, and with the field aggregation, that's all,
and we're looking to drop all the problems in that relationship.
I personally have been charged for me for the UH-60 Calcutta District Program,
which is a GSA, and the federal government is full-life sites supported by
a little factor of encouragement.
Build a life school, build a training facility, build a maintenance facility,
build a full life sector support for both the Jordan and Saudi Arabia.
Next slide, please.
For our value proposition, we want to bring community growth, training, jobs,
and services for the business, we want to bring community growth,
jobs for the Americans, jobs for this way to take, and expanding a mind-resistant airport.
We would like to bring friends to the F&P out, the most obvious ones,
called it, in group 66, all past made to money, even through the air.
I think that's a kind of full-life together.
And we just like bringing in one of the hundred and eight-to-five training
maintenance, and it's just a job of the five to two years.
So, our vast, in this way, we found a thing that will happen if you can turn it over and do flight training school, maintenance, or bare facility, a guidance facility, so that we can get to try our own computer, and write for our near term, through this 69 days, if you have proof of place, food and sublet from a rise, we bring 9 to 13 to 13 immediately.
So, we'll leave the can, we have a matter of test and maintenance.
So, we'll program here two years before we win the gym in the past, and we'll do the flight set, and we'll leave the can in context, and we'll bring this fuel gots, and the three four fuel gots.
Receptionist, we wanted to have the division of the freezes.
More of an extension, eventually we have a little bit of facility, but I'll be great to see you over here, and bring in the name of this little drive.
And just a little bit more of the customer experience that people are looking for in the aviation industry.
They bring in the research tendency.
She's got a couple of people that are already working there for movies, and I don't want them to stay on them.
First, we're trying to use them and we'll bring additional factors that can happen to that facility.
And obviously, we're going to be great, and it's important that we can do it.
And these higher things out, also, what's important, some of the needed things that are happening with that facility,
the clothes and some of the current happening, as opposed to the regular.
You've got jobs, and there's a support line.
A two, three, four, and then another one.
Thanks.
Thank you.
So the features we're going to be hiring on the training, new labor force, training
education groups.
We've been in that high school, not only for adults, and veterans, and we've come in,
but we're looking at the partner with the local auto-parenting school.
We've been in a junior in the senior high school education program at our office.
We've been learning the airplane, the community, the simulator, and send it to those programs.
We've been in Toronto, in Toronto, and in Switzerland.
We've been in Toronto anyway, in Toronto.
I think we're going to be able to, again, drive an additional job to try to locate
when you recycle those airplanes.
There are going to be some parts of the policy that we have to refurbish and bring back to market
and we'll have dedicated that to following the Southwest, for several other or air-bound partners with the Internet.
So I'm going to bring the five state of jobs, just to recycling and refurbish and parts.
It would be in that beautiful facility in the country.
Or we can build it, we can make a ring of roses, and we can build it.
We've built it.
The English traffic would be up.
We would provide a very simple key for the city's driver to new up.
And in order to try to balance the community, create everything, scale it like a force here.
Interesting half story.
Today, I was working out of the facility now.
The town is fire.
Five or one.
Some of the gentlemen, they can't believe he worked out this week.
Oh, he can't think.
Thank you.
The facility.
His, the brother-in-law, is starting now in Tulsa.
It weren't to be the, and he's even getting in.
Well, they were signing.
He was going to be back in nowhere to move.
He was going to be right back to the league.
As a poor generation, my name is English.
Are you looking at me?
H.K.A.A.C. and my partner.
And if that gets out of the league, I think it was a better ride.
He just happened to me when he began his position here.
But that was interesting.
But that's interesting.
That's part of the session.
We need to be able to say that.
Thank you.
I'm going to do some new jobs.
Then, of course, if you were taken into practice this,
anything that you have here, for you know, it's the hardest community.
So, when you grow things, you have to, at this near to come,
for example, with cargo.
You can throw out an animal from here.
You can throw out a student.
You can throw out a student from here.
Just like you do with that.
I mean, just like you do with the Tulsa.
They have 700 to 900 kids, hundreds of their, every 9 to 8 months.
The school alone is about 120 to 100% out of public.
If you need a one-way program, which is what you're looking at,
those students don't live in the night.
They have to do the park, and how you're looking at it.
Transportation.
They contribute to entertainment.
Anything.
Thank you.
Yes.
I can treat surgery.
I can treat your whole body.
Did it come part of you?
In some of them they said, you can put, but they're, but they're, you're out.
Some of those activities like that, you can come part of you.
You then, well, they're here.
They're just poor.
You need to contact them.
You know, all areas are comfortable.
Next slide.
I don't think that's it.
That's it.
So we, first of all, go ahead and ask questions.
Well, thank you.
My nephews are retired.
You can't curl an airport.
She flies for a set of questions now.
And I was actually just talking about the shortage of pilots.
And I can't get to my brother's retired.
But I can't.
He's also a stress report.
So.
I'm just like, many of them in this race.
You know, you have people who are right.
Think of the disease.
You can live in this gap.
It's talented.
You know, you've got the younger.
You've got the younger.
It's a bit strange.
Now, it's been weird.
It's not being.
It can't.
And so there's almost like there's a reason.
Well, we don't want to have those kind of issues.
Eric.
It's really.
Really.
He said that we're doing program.
We're going to program all those schools for engineers and seniors.
What's going on with the talk that you're going to.
I think he talks with the chief of the friend right now to do it.
We get you know, why not?
in the AIDS world.
So it's part of that, as I was telling you the origin of the Philippines,
you'd be asked to try to determine, honor, and earned,
and not need to need to think of him to try that.
I think the high school world is what we're looking at.
Aircarinaegas, we're looking at private, piloted to a global program,
in engineering and industry such as peer nutrition and check all of them
to hear from operations, the rest of the programs,
side of the threats to agricultural towers.
To the public, the sport is to the public,
to the public, to the high school.
Their next question, they have the video game program,
how long they're aware that they're just $100,000,
and we do that as an entry,
what it plays for our program.
There's a huge push for drone and agriculture now,
and we see it as a bit of it.
So that's why we start talking to the customer,
because they're here on the community.
So we see this as a phase approach,
obviously the first phase would be the fields,
the air, the foot services,
and bringing it in.
and at part 1.45, 9.5 to 10.5 operations.
You've got about right in there along the folks
picking, laying these in those for days.
So you're basically not talking to you
to try, while we can hear this vibe,
you have to think of it, have it to break down
on that home, if there's been a thousand of what you've had.
So that those are, that's our biggest party right now.
To secure these supplements from there,
You know, on the ground, the people who are concerned,
you can now drive in the market and business development.
Drive in the market.
And what she talks about at least what we propose is that the city
entered a long-term lease with a rise that had your foundation.
And then that could have been some of the police
to argue, gentlemen, so that's come to the end.
But through that lease, you would have a benchmark inside of the lease.
It requires sort of a re-firmers in the area.
It requires to be certain,
and then we work out the FEDO of the new costs,
but please remember, we are non-profit.
We are about right to the end of the year,
50 million holidays.
So I have to ask that if you think about it,
I have one action on the city,
but when you think about it,
please think of all that in consideration.
We wouldn't be part of it.
We don't have all the answers,
but I think this is one of the key to know.
When she started about 10 to 7,
three of this community,
we'd have to extend them on the way as well.
And that brings us to the concern of the community.
One, the Christian county,
the county can see us in the eastern hand of the B.A.
and then that has become a new road to the city's plan.
We would re-locate the stock of the building at our cost.
One of the things I can talk about,
I thought about doing what we would actually destroy the junior high in our cost,
and re-locate the stock of the kids there, to the pieces.
But we would need to extend them on with the job that they would want to do.
And please understand my thought about that.
They can burn every day.
They can't go into the past few,
they're recycling the building one, two,
a year.
I don't miss out on the month.
So you're talking about 20 people,
big birds.
Of course, you're not dead.
I'm not talking about crying.
But if you look at a choir,
some revitalization is one way currently you have to think
and everyone will ensure that as well.
And so, you know, I mentioned our heavy equipment operations.
We're going to use our students.
So we're going to maintain hopefully over our costs.
We're going to use evidence equipment at the company in Missouri.
There's the biggest cap we've ever shared in the world.
And also for fiduciary purposes,
we can use hard-earned books that are counted on the job.
So all of the funds are in any context.
So coming to the end.
So there's broken inspiration for us.
So that's the case for you.
You have the phrase, the phrase that I'm interested in,
and the rest of it.
I think it's going to run like this,
but it's going to be in the middle of the town or more.
I would refer to this,
that's the path of reasons of this.
But that requires the county,
and the county is going to participate if you participate.
And then that's going to have to be a public,
there's going to be something certain about your interest.
But I think all of that can be able to come into the community.
It's not an advice veteran.
It really isn't about changing the landscape point.
So the next 22nd Street,
there we have to go away.
That portion might be there, actually.
I absolutely did.
They'd run into the scenario.
But what we would do is we could close the,
the brain, the world of the knockoffs.
It would divide to be a beautiful side.
You can take the eastern hand,
remediates, and then the runway side.
Build you a new road in there.
We're looking to talk to you.
Nice to meet you wherever.
I would refer to it.
And our costs exceed as you put it.
You take down a junior high.
And we look at it.
That's at the school board.
The public schools.
It's assuming that costs that didn't listen to that.
They are.
Okay.
So there you go.
Yeah.
I'd like to both.
I'd like to play outside.
I'd like to talk to you.
I would like to hear exactly whom every day,
that's over time come here and develop
those efforts and good jobs there.
That is the big focus in this,
applying kilograms like that.
Things a year of flying,
files
very, nanoparties.
Very, very figure.
Some you would like to,
some you can consider real thing
where there's, a year of COVID,
So that goes to the public and it means they're going to need to take it.
On the top part of it, it goes to the public.
I don't want a lot of support.
We need to find our students.
So, are we going to work with the school?
Where was it going to be?
It will be in the United States.
But why not?
So, no.
We're going to talk about things to be part of things.
So, you should...
I'm going to turn into Jim and the second one.
I'm going to also have a campaign for the city of Jerusalem.
But we really want to support you.
When we historically accurate aired there at the inside of the museum, we'll see you.
So, we're going to be pretty inspired by it.
It would actually be the school.
The fight school will start to kind of talk about the schools at all.
But yes, I'm certain the other to talk to him around to any one of these issues.
I would like that, because we're being the ones who besting you to be a partner of this.
And we would like to, we won't keep our kids here too.
Absolutely.
And I know our kids would like to have that conversation.
And it's impossible.
Well, I'm certainly here in the Bible to make some of that.
You have to get the book.
Sure, it really looks like there was a meeting in the past.
Just a moment.
There's a council.
You know, schools on how to turn your program into a night program.
You might not have that meeting today.
We're going to be sitting with all of them.
But, um, in fact, too, we'd be purchasing the simulators versus the near crack.
And building out several of those schools.
That's where our things are going to be applied.
As well as around the health and health and your work in the health of the group.
So, on the health path there, and then putting some hurts of our service,
as well as, hey, not necessarily enterprise.
But, and then additional room for our service.
So, we think we're expecting things coming back.
So, I would like to...
Our recycled project isn't predicated by the fact that we actually didn't run away.
So, we could actually drop those plenty of different locations with the whole,
and then shrug the parts in the infrastructure.
And then, at that point, we would prefer that money staying on the end,
but it was not...
If it's not being, well, we could, especially in the program.
But, I don't know.
But, I don't think about it.
But, we definitely talk about it, and see what we get done.
Like, the chief didn't work on this for a couple years.
It doesn't end.
You know, those streets that you're right there by your airport.
So, what do you think?
I think, on the expansion, there were a lot of hurdles to overcome.
Definitely the whole.
And we're looking at a 1200 feet.
A runway.
It was like, what you have to do to build their top view of work.
And then, unfortunately, there were a lot of protection,
and I don't know what you saw that day.
It was a long time ago.
But, it's an individual.
There are a couple of buildings.
It's a building.
There are four different ways.
A great thing for our board.
We have tried numerous things to try to develop our board.
Talk to a couple of developers and ways to increase revenue and increase use and
arrive on set of the best programs.
But, it doesn't matter.
I know the Board of the Courthorpegg, and it talks from several times.
And they're going to.
So, we have my name, which we're going to write on the field.
with it, with G Street, to have to be a Mexican at all.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
the last place I heard, I'd believe there's a part of the area
around that side, so it would be the people who wanted to
pack you over there, to walk around for a row.
They could do that because of the five-land,
for a rough one or whatever, it goes over there.
Just a little part here and there,
we would sell from the main area of the main area of the main area,
over there, but you wouldn't have to ban the G Street at all.
I know, per place, we just look hurt,
people eyes, and he's talked about a restaurant,
and the people do that in their hours.
They don't apply for it.
They're home to another airport that has a restaurant.
I don't remember it, it's one of the best thing about flying.
You know, flying everywhere to the deep line, sir.
That's a huge thing I engaged in.
People flying in just to walk around street grammar.
I'm flying in the checker lodge, man there,
and get there.
That's just a point in my grip and a lot of people are there.
I think it would definitely increase our traffic,
and make my money work.
So today, when you look at work for us today,
right now we don't have an action item.
We just wanted to inform the council,
and we've had several conversations.
They presented to the board questions for the families,
and so the council of the conversations
for the community a little bit,
we want to make sure the council is aware of the plans,
and make sure to bring in a formal decorator,
documents, listerings, and we all day have been very much work.
So, you know,
but then we learn things.
We want the council to be aware and for a future road.
So, I don't know if it's exciting for me to see opportunities like this.
It's just to come up for us.
Especially for us to be here.
That's something big that a lot of work is.
I don't have anything to say here.
This will give you a lot of energy to do that.
So, I'm going to take you to supply jobs.
We'll give you that.
I know we have builder in the house that we're probably,
he's not paying attention to.
He's here talking about building something to buy.
So, they're probably, we're able to build more houses here.
So, they can really have a chair about our back force.
So, we're going to go with the international flights.
We'll attach with the bicycle.
It would definitely bring in the team.
We can bring foreign students in from different countries.
We'll be asking for you.
What we're doing in our bus.
We...
You know, it's pretty money.
Yep.
That's close.
I mean, you said, you got 15 million, and we had zero.
I think like a way.
But it's a good one.
Yeah.
Something maybe to keep in mind too.
I mean, I'm all that the wonderful thing is that they've brought out.
Bring this in the music.
You know, they talk about the music.
And then it's something that all of us have dealt with,
for the five or five years.
What can we do with that property?
You know, it's a significant amount of property here in my hand.
And that's a very significant amount of property.
And the limitations comes from the potential, or what we know
to have contaminants.
There's a division on the site that we encourage.
That's currently remediated multiple parties.
But you can't limit what we're going to do with that site.
And so to have an opportunity with somebody coming in and seeing
the potential in what they can do in the service level.
So that's currently what a great use for these property
that may have limitations to use.
That would turn the negative into a thing that has a problem.
So I think it's really exciting to do that.
The digital use of the property.
I believe that we want to talk to you about it.
We have an opportunity to talk to you about it exciting.
So whenever you're talking about recycling these carecrafts,
you tell them this man what?
That's him.
And then what do you do with him?
That's very, very, very, very handy with him.
But the most important thing to remember is
for a foundation that's a great sustainability.
But in the purpose, we've brought to provide a job for our veterans.
The goal here is to get to the DOD and the VA.
And help transition veterans into the work of our tribe.
Got him going home with the DOD for the VA to take it to the site.
So the recycling process we built the store for some of us there.
It's our mission to stop what's going on.
He's still getting his point.
But for that data, that requires the main technique,
the parts of the home they're going to have.
And it's a win-win situation that everybody,
because now they're not paying the store somewhere in this.
So it's perfect.
In keeping our veterans busy, it is, is it cool,
especially our combat veterans.
We lose them when they transition out of the old territory.
And we're working with the verticals that we're going to be trying to do.
So when she talks about it, we're going to get those hundred people.
We don't have a hundred people.
And there's still a whole bunch of those jobs.
We're going to work with the DOD trying to help those young people
to transition into the work.
And bring them around.
You know, this is a nice campaign for several meetings.
It's awful.
You've got four thousand years, you've got a lot of taxes.
You've got a total of $1,000.
All of those things are remarkable, right?
You can move that signal, you know,
you've got the recreation areas,
and you can enter the different pictures.
I don't think the street,
it's not a street closure, it's a rerout.
Because they're going to build the brand industry.
It's not a reward.
I don't know.
Oh, I can.
It's not a reward.
But you come in and put it in a whole big way,
so you look a fun thing in my idea and it looks like
like right now to do a secure that and put together
the nice thing to expand in, if we own,
just a lot of things to do with a partnership with the prize,
I think, step-by-step, everyone's calling,
to engage this in the Internet.
And this is a relatively different way, right now.
That's why the world better build the world.
We're going to invest that much.
We're going to invest that money in the year and about 40% more or so than the one we're going to have to say that we're going to take a little job close and move by nicely.
So it's really to humanitarian effort in our view.
We want to really reach our matters from the changes.
We don't want to go home with others.
We only want to pursue a side of the package.
I said you see last year we stopped 60, 60, and so I didn't even know.
We reached over 60,000 of them across the country.
It's important for us to continue to make strides in our efforts from humanitarian standards.
I like it.
I don't know.
That airplane there is far more our community's history that's wasting away.
And we've talked about several times.
We're going to figure out how to revitalize it.
And I keep it from many more generations.
There are community.
There's a way that that costs us a dime.
So I like it.
Of course, we're going to go off on our first talk about it.
What you guys want to do is the police agreement that we'll go there.
Miley asked for the talk of my opposed rules.
I think that they're a presentation to see me.
Nothing gets why not.
Let me just build your hand along with both of us.
I think there's room for all of us.
You think about it.
So why do you guys have real community?
And the city is the host community.
I think there's room for all of us.
I bet Dr. Staffer would get on the board with us.
We would go by sister.
We've actually talked about the Staffer.
I think Dr. Staffer is patiently waiting to see when the candidates sit there.
But I think it's all about the rules.
It's so much of a challenge for the county's way of us
that a word in Russia that a law foreign demand
to our percent of the US, so you're helping see what it gets here.
Thank you.
Thanks.
President, sorry.
President, we're not on the recognition.
We're seeing a job in the United Nations and the sign of the
region of the second priority, and the sign of the decision of the
environmental interest.
So this is a presentation of the city's government
I'm telling the business mission, as you call the first day.
I'm going to include in what you can write now,
as a picture of the proposed reflex,
and I just have to write in the developer.
The developer was here tonight,
and it was so surprised that you got additional questions
that were there.
I also take, you guys, to watch some pictures,
to kind of the visual, or the operator's app,
that also let you know what the zoning is,
how to go round this property.
Also, you're good.
You know, I'll pay for it.
I'll pay for it.
I'll do a lot.
So there's heard because there are two lots.
First heard, the 1616B Northwest is a lot
that has a house on it currently,
and then right, and the adjacent to that,
is a garage from Portland.
It's been that way for effort,
and years and years and years and years together.
Before any of our time,
that was a garage apartment that was never done
in residential multifamily.
It's a fairly, because it lost its legal life
in Portland status,
but we're trying to get into what is not being connected to it.
Their desire to interact as a garage,
but in the end they can have to get a result.
So they're running to the reason of that loss,
1616B Northwest,
and you'll have a lot in the north of that,
and they need to own that,
and how soon there's a full time in the house,
or in the minimum,
many years ago,
and in the previous owners,
apart in that block, you know, can be found.
That's just cool, lots.
The house in the north of Portland,
part of the parking lot of two lots.
For the house was on the north end of Portland,
they were raised in the valley,
also one of them.
They were raised in the new west,
on the north too much to the lake,
and they were raised in the west park.
And that whole block, two and a half sec.
Let's do a bunch of things, your work.
Yes, of course.
Something that came up to the conversation
on the first and the second slide is
that you'd like to start with being this block
and the zoning that we're requesting allows them to deal.
A unit that is a total of 28 units
where we can develop or let us know
if they're saying, no, I think it'll be 20 units
where he's 14 units where he's on which side.
Which is a really nice size of a few legs.
For a unit, per unit, quick.
Yes, four, seven, three, cover.
Do you have more to up there?
Sure.
A little, we do.
We're on a student's, I'm happy to do some
adventure questions.
I have forwarder, I can see that there's so many
nice legs that it was actually built in the ocean.
So I believe that's 12, I'm sure.
I feel like that will wrap it up.
Three, that one, two, that each side of it,
one back there has a full touch of shark,
on which it's built as a handicap, generally.
How do you make sure we go a little bit
of your back right?
What's your history here in the country?
OK.
Short version, graduated in the high school,
what I had these school came to her point, came to me.
A class in state of heat, for built-in airlines,
but a set of years from going back to school,
to try and figure 37, 37, 37, 37, 37,
built their lives, and set them there.
What back to hospital, mayor of Illinois, Virginia,
Johnlin, 2000, lived there for the last 21 years,
16 year-old, boy, 14 year-old girl, 80.
Five of the year-old boy, and a seven year-old son,
and figure it by a teamhouse, electric past year,
and he had a big hospital church in the new day of UC,
and thought of my amount, we put it there,
we put one of the very best of all our new dimensions.
We're here since February, last week,
we have all the problems in the commerce of my amount,
my amount of preparation, this month,
built by the new houses of an age group in commerce,
permanent, and low-level.
And so we were trying to buy companies,
as we have over the last few years in chocolate, the ocean, carbon.
And so, before our leadership parties and the ability to move the problems over the next few years,
we have to invest in the committee and the committee here for quite some time.
And because of the progress we've parted out of last three years, so we're going to decide to come here.
I think that's your question.
My wife and I have a decision on time, but we'll never ready anything to do with people.
So the opportunity to move this, yes sir.
This is a nice, the need to build this, go my house, and not be afraid of it.
So, I actually just want to do what my house.
The need to build more, the need to know more about this.
I'll do it.
Our community to be thousands, and it's not like we're any more.
So, you might have a question.
We can do a further view to amend the agenda right which to refer to the ordinance.
And then things that we've covered in the plan, and as I remember, and then we've done exactly what that means to me.
So, we don't need to do an agenda that we have.
The work that's proposed ordinance.
I think it's lots of different things changing.
There is a particular framework to practice.
But you want to approve the importance that you have to copy it also.
Take this.
Excuse me.
Hi.
So, go find Parker.
I was normally mistaken, but I've got assignments.
I've got a problem.
Here's what you call and she remembered.
I've got a sign here.
So, let me sign here to change that.
Now it's their place.
You're signing here with simply being a ministerial.
Okay.
Thank you.
Take care.
I was in the packet.
It was her closet in my garage.
to have to be offered for public health. It's also for high scrap metal value, or a
authorizing construction to text his little equation.
What's theability of the wrong?
They don't know about that.
One point five.
Two point five.
One point six.
So you have that list in front of you.
I hope there are no questions because Chris is on here.
She's the one who knows the interest.
There is one piece of equipment there that is still functioning.
It means it holds to that to be something that you can do.
So, if you're a minor shaming, it's basically everything else on the list.
You know what you're trying to do with us.
But let's go to the point five.
Go to the point five.
Right.
We can try to use the computer.
I'll show you how to use it.
That's what we can solve.
Thanks.
Through the past.
We'll do this.
Here we go.
Make most of your movies.
Right.
This is the one.
These two.
Five.
Fever.
Double.
Five.
Eleven.
The intention is very important.
People will ask for a number of more importantly,
to be able to keep that.
They can be important to the object.
Really.
Services.
We can use it.
We'll run.
We'll play your project.
Or we'll know what we're going to play.
So this is just something.
This is the city side.
Because that's street staffing.
I'll sign.
So, is that the last day of the release?
I'll make much into a room.
Does that mean?
Mark, Mark, Mark.
Go to the report.
Mark, David, Scott, and he said that.
Well, Tom Carrack, and then went to a stature day.
So, Mayor, you have to remember this as an item that has not been to the air.
It's a item that has not been to the air.
It's a kind of factory.
You can pass on it.
That's a truck or an instrument.
Tom Carrack realized that we could maybe use an execution room
for the nation to be in the fiscal year for our contract.
This one year may be different.
So, we went into the room on there and we were going to research that.
We were going to return to that.
We were going to return to the contract.
We were going to get into the municipal park this one year.
At the end of June.
So, there's the wish.
We can pass.
There.
So this was supposed to be in the 16 exact works.
So I'm being mayor and I'm hoping to end this.
So I was in the moment of meeting with the gentleman,
who invited another who's not this spring and they,
who was the process of building.
And then the other question that we asked was,
how do we get it?
How do we get it?
There's not a set of where we can do my own house on May 3.
You weren't out of the word.
I was like, okay.
You were not out of the word.
I don't feel the mess in here.
I'm just asking.
I'm saying shit.
I'm going to treat that.
No thanks.
For a kind of snack, the reason why.
I've been, other than safety.
I mean, I've been, I've been.
You want your two?
Yeah, but have you ever been to Jay?
That's too, definitely.
No one ever goes to the village now.
The big ones go on time.
So the question becomes, if we don't, if you can't be burned out, that's fun, what's
it?
Do we need to do anything special to organize it?
So, what's happening is they're organizing it in harsh general, out of the casino
on May 13th and 14th.
And we probably know, but the burnout thing was really a joke, but the question was a serious question was about doing it.
Bruce, 9th, 9th, 9th, 13th, and then the Apollo Shadows, what do you think happens most of the day?
Well, it's part of the love process that the crew's buying, and we're just something to coordinate, and we'll work with what we need to do.
Yeah, I don't think there's any, this is just for people that the shelter rides off, not to run into one area.
I think we did several of the class here, that there's different people who are going out.
And really, this takes someone to get on and start a PR, or to raise one, and so the question that I was asked to bring is, do we contact them?
Get that started in the room, do you know that?
I think I've done both of them.
I've done that way.
So if you want to put that in your bus, that's our routine.
Certainly not. We important.
Perfect.
I appreciate it. Thank you.
Good.
Thank you.
I'm good.
I want to make it.
I'll look back at your show.
We're going to want to be teens in the afternoon day.
I'm not going to do that, though.
So, thank you all, where I stand out at the end of the day.
People are going to do a fight with me.
Easy to record.
It's a rule.
A very favorable day.
I'm going to say goodbye.
Regarding the appeal.
And that's something that we'll be looking into further.
I mean, we don't have a lot of comments.
I just wanted to just be seated today.
The rule is not eight minutes.
So we need to go through and I guess that.
Obviously, we'll have not to do these kinds of things.
That's further.
But if it is, it was a rule in our favor.
And so we'll consider, we'll need to be considered further.
I want to talk about the presentation.
Other than that.
By certain, we wanted to mention that on the 24th next month day.
Our work study is going to be at the Colman Theatre.
That we're 30.
E.M.
So we're going to start talking really.
It's a very long journey to get through.
And I think it'll be a great opportunity to kind of touch with me.
We're going to be discussing the Colman.
And we missed the Colman.
And when I found out that historically,
we've actually had meetings at Colman.
And we're going to be also actually a few days.
I tell you a great place, there's no need to gather there, and we'll explain you what the topic is.
In the end, we'll have a discussion about the moment, we'll move on towards that.
And we'll go ahead.
Good afternoon.
Thank you.
I see.